Last week, they had their final date...
before the final decision.
- That was the final date.
- The final date.
Some couples confirmed...
- their feelings for each other.
- Yes.
But for some, they've come to face...
- yet another crisis.
- Everything has been reset.
It seems like that for some.
- But they only have one day left.
- Yes.
The scary fact is,
today is the final episode.
(What a pity.)
The complicated romance at Yeon House...
is finally nearing its end.
Before the final decision,
how will things play out,
and who will end up with who?
We won't know until it ends.
(The final night before the final decision)
(Yun So and Si Won's room)
Did you have fun today?
Today,
we talked about a lot of serious stuff.
- Really?
- Very realistic things.
- Like marriage?
- Yes.
I do think I should talk about it at least once too.
- You haven't, have you?
- No.
But once you talk about it...
I was honestly a bit scared,
so I couldn't bring it up at first.
- Right, me too.
- Because honestly,
we're not seeing each other yet.
- Right.
- To talk about the topic...
It feels like a burden to me,
- to us, honestly.
- Right.
But...
But when you think about it,
from her perspective,
it's natural to talk about it.
If she's someone who wants to get married at some point,
she'd definitely think about that the first thing.
That was what I thought.
He's trying to be in Ju Hee's shoes.
Frankly, I can't say I'd marry her right now.
- Obviously.
- Yes, we can't get married now.
Exactly. It's impossible.
How am I supposed to get through this?
I honestly have no idea.
I don't know what's the best answer I can give her...
in this situation.
(Yun So thinks about the best answer he can give.)
I see.
I don't think Yun So was all that interested in...
the idea of getting married to begin with.
I think that could've brought upon his reaction.
That's right, to be honest.
He's busy having fun.
(Meanwhile, in Ju Hee's room)
Is she crying?
Who? Ju Hee?
(Sitting up)
Why is she crying?
(Ju Hee was crying under the blanket.)
(That afternoon, Ju Hee had a date with Yun So.)
(I feel like our conversation is going nowhere.)
I felt that for you, getting married...
(It looked like you were in a hurry to get married.)
(That's why I'm scared to ask you as well.)
(Thinking)
She must've gotten very hurt then.
That wasn't what he meant.
You should ask and talk it out.
(Her date with Yun So didn't work out well.)
(Knocking)
Is it just Ji Hye inside?
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Are you crying?
No, if she does that, Ju Hee will burst into tears.
(Looking at Ji Seung makes her bottled up emotions emerge again.)
Why are you crying?
All the older girls are shocked.
I just feel like a complete idiot.
Why do you feel like an idiot?
You're not. Why would you think so?
I lead all our conversations.
When you're with him?
And he says he likes it when I do that.
But when I asked about the future plans,
he kept saying irrelevant things.
It seemed that he felt uncomfortable.
- I don't know what he wants.
- He didn't give you assurance?
- Go on.
- He kept saying it was hard.
That it was hard to talk about the future.
It's harder to talk about it because he has feelings for me.
I keep saying what I want to say...
and do what I want to do.
He gets flustered,
and my confidence starts to drop.
The misunderstanding is building up.
One thing I felt clearly is...
that it all comes from the experience.
It's not about him as a person.
He could be fine after several years.
But now, he is so inexperienced.
So he'd never act in a way we'd want him to.
- That's right.
- I really tried...
to look past the age.
- And look at the rest.
- But...
I don't know.
(The reality hits her hard on the last night at Yeon House.)
It's a dilemma.
It keeps...
Whether Yun So's words were conveyed right or wrong,
she's come to realize the situation.
At Yeon House,
all the older women and younger men are blooming their love,
so she mustered up some courage.
But that illusion suddenly shattered.
(All her courage disappeared.)
Then they should...
- really level with each other.
- All the more reason to talk.
(The final day at Yeon House has started.)
The final day does come, after all.
(They've only left with the final decision tonight.)
(A message is only sent to the younger men.)
(It's the day of the final decision.)
(Send the name of the older woman you'd like to talk more with.)
There's a date before the final decision?
There should be. They need to talk one last time.
Finally, at the end, the younger men get to choose.
It's the last chance they have.
They need to talk it out well.
They need to resolve every issue.
It's Jin Wu.
I can tell from the back of his head that it's Jin Wu.
I must've gotten very attached to him.
(Jin Wu is waiting for the older woman...)
(to talk with one last time.)
(Which older woman did Jin Wu want to talk with one last time?)
(It's Jin Young.)
Jin Wu.
You're here.
Did you wait long?
Not so much.
Really?
- Thank you.
- I've already ordered the drink.
Did you expect me here?
- Yes.
- I'm sure you did.
Yes. I knew you'd be here.
How do you feel? Are you okay?
- What?
- Are you feeling okay?
- Am I feeling okay?
- Better than yesterday?
Much better than yesterday.
Yesterday...
Yesterday, it was...
really hard for me.
I wasn't in my right mind.
Really...
You...
You comforting me really helped me a lot.
Thank you for saying that.
- This is embarrassing.
- It really helped a lot.
They've comforted each other.
(Jin Young and Jin Wu found solace in each other.)
When I first got the text to hold the hand of my date...
and leave the place, I thought for a very long time.
- Do you remember?
- Yes. I remember everything.
You remember? I was considering between you and Jun Han.
Did you know that?
- I had no idea.
- Really?
- I thought you'd no interest in me.
(The first time Jin Young and Jin Wu met)
(Jin Young could choose her date, )
(and she was torn between Jin Wu and Jun Han.)
(As soon as I saw Jin Wu's face, I thought he was very handsome.)
(So he caught my eyes.)
He was so handsome that I couldn't look at him.
The weather is nice today.
(But Jin Young chose Jun Han.)
(Holding gently)
(And Jin Wu was unaware of Jin Young's conflict.)
You didn't even look to my side.
Even if I had chosen you then,
we might not have had...
a fun conversation like this...
because your head was occupied by someone else.
It all is what ifs, but if that had happened,
things would've become a whole lot more complicated.
- Now...
- I can't imagine.
It would've been more difficult emotionally...
than the past four days.
Things have already been very difficult for me as they were.
That's why I said that yesterday. When you...
It really broke my heart when you asked...
why I'd treat you so nicely.
There's no reason to treating someone well and reciprocating it.
I treated you well because I wanted to,
and because you deserve to be well-treated.
It's been so long since I've heard something like that,
so I felt so bad for you.
That's why I said...
I did see myself in you.
Watching how Jin Young suffered,
I didn't want her to waste her time...
wallowing in negative emotions.
She broke down in front of me.
And I know how hard it is.
So I didn't want her to cry.
(He saw how he himself suffered in Jin Young, whom he likes.)
I just wanted to take care of you.
I didn't want you to cry.
You cried so sadly in front of me,
and it would've been impossible for me to smile...
or stay nonchalant at that.
I'm sorry about that too.
Anyway, you've said you had feelings for me,
but I cried in front of you...
because I liked another guy.
- That doesn't hurt me at all.
- That was terrible of me.
At that moment, I just wanted to take care of you.
I wanted to become someone who you could rely on at that time.
That was enough then.
I've been telling you...
that it was random...
and that I couldn't understand...
you were being so nice to me...
all of a sudden.
Your affection for me...
felt so fake.
When you were treating me well,
it felt like too much.
Right.
But...
we talked for a long time yesterday.
And you were consistent.
That's when I realized...
you were the sincerest participant...
among everyone here.
(You were the sincerest person here.)
That's when I realized that.
That you were genuine about this.
That I was mistaken.
What if they become a couple after this?
Love doesn't always begin with romantic attraction.
It can also start when two people...
comfort and rely on each other...
through shared pain and wounds.
- Indeed.
- Yes.
(Pondering)
Do you think you can see me again after all this?
You?
(She can't seem to answer.)
As a man?
Obviously.
To be honest,
I...
have been into Jeong Won for too long.
Just because...
I was rejected yesterday.
I don't think I can change my mind overnight.
So, you're not sure who you're going to choose...
in the final decision yet?
I'm torn.
I'm torn, yes.
I can't say for sure that I'll choose you...
or Jeong Won.
I think it depends on what my criteria are...
for the final decision.
She didn't leave him any room yesterday,
but she can't decide today.
I already told you what my criteria would be.
It's not just about the eight days in this program.
I'm considering my everyday life and future outside of this.
My decision will be based on that.
(Jin Young has a lot on her mind before the final decision.)
But my only wish is...
that no other man...
will be involved in your decision.
I hope that you'll pick me...
solely because I'm the first person...
you want to see...
when we leave.
If you're going to pick me, I mean.
(She has a mysterious look on her face.)
(Will his final sincere words change her mind?)
(Meanwhile, another man is waiting for an older woman.)
(Si Won)
(Grinning)
- Hi.
Your outfit looks different today.
- That's right. Yes.
- Right?
Did you wait long?
Not really.
- Really?
- Yes.
Short enough to drink this much coffee.
You didn't have to wait that long, then.
- It's the last day.
- I know.
Doesn't the weather feel like it's the last day?
It feels like the day of the final decision.
- Do you feel serious?
- I do.
It's been so sunny until yesterday.
- I know.
- Right?
(Hesitating)
So, did you make up your mind?
Of course.
- Really?
- Yes.
I thought you were going somewhere else before this.
- Really?
- Yes.
- No one would ask me out, though.
- Really?
There's no one else.
How do you think you'll feel after this?
After this...
- I'll probably be busy.
- A busy life.
- Yes, a busy life.
- Yes.
I do wonder what we'll turn out to be.
- So do I.
- Right?
- It's such an unusual situation.
- Right.
I think it'll be...
- more awkward outside.
- Right.
- When we suddenly meet.
It'll be awkward at first.
- The moment we meet.
- Yes.
Both our ears might turn red.
- This whole area will turn red.
- Exactly.
I think so.
So,
I kind of...
want to go...
- on a date outside.
- So do I.
I wonder how it feels.
- Same here.
- Yes.
Without all the cameras.
- I think it'll be fun.
- I think so too.
It'll probably feel real...
- at that moment.
- Yes, it'll hit us.
I agree.
- I had a question for you.
- Okay.
Do you plan on getting married?
(Flustered)
- I think it's like this.
- Okay.
I can't say...
that I'm totally...
- against marriage.
- Okay.
But I may not get married if I don't find anyone...
I want to marry.
But my basic idea is...
that I want to get married someday.
- But right now...
- If you find someone to marry?
But I'm not talking...
about this year or next year.
When I find someone I love...
and our timing is right,
I want to get married. That's my idea.
So, it's more about the person than time.
(It's more about the person than time.)
- What about you? Say...
- Yes?
We end up dating outside of this.
And I said to you, "I want to get married next year."
Next year?
You'll be 26 then. How do you think you'll feel?
- I'll be 26?
- Yes.
I don't know what kind of person I'll be in a year,
but when I'm 26...
Well, it's not that I care about my age.
But it's likely that I won't be prepared enough.
- Realistically speaking.
- Right.
But once I'm ready,
I want to get married...
regardless of my age.
When I'm with you,
the age...
(The age difference)
doesn't really hit me.
I'm not even certain if you're really 25.
It just feels like you're my age.
- You're more up to date than I am.
- I know!
- I feel younger.
- Exactly.
(A guy born in 2002 who knows nothing about Gen Z)
But when I picture it,
I realize...
that it won't be easy.
- Naturally.
- Yes.
And you've never dated anyone younger than you.
Never.
And a guy who's 12 years younger popped out...
and started making a move on you.
- He literally popped out.
- Exactly.
Why did you have to be 25?
Why?
I think it's natural that you're worried.
But when I'm with you,
I forget about the age gap.
I also think this works because of that.
- Right?
- Yes.
If I noticed the age difference when I was with you,
I'd be worried that it might not work.
- But I didn't sense any of that.
- Right.
So, I...
want to see you...
- Outside of this?
- Yes.
- I'd like to.
- Me too.
- We have to try grilled hagfish.
- Grilled hagfish.
I should pay for that.
I'm a big eater.
(Yu Jin and Si Won finished their last talk...)
So am I.
Would you be okay spending 1,000 dollars there?
(before the final decision.)
(What's going on at Yeon House?)
(Ju Hee and Ji Hye are sitting in the vanity room together.)
(Sighing)
No!
Why are you sighing again?
Last night was fatal.
It was Yun So's fault.
But when it comes to dating a younger guy,
that's part of the fun.
He makes a slip of the tongue,
so you scold him, spank him,
and correct him.
He makes another mistake,
you glare at him,
and he goes, "I'm sorry." It goes like this.
(Ju Hee has a lot on her mind and steps out.)
She's going to educate him.
(Where is she headed?)
Yun So!
She's here.
- Ju Hee, I'm here.
- Hey.
I thought you were in this room.
(They came into a room for a chat.)
- You can sit there.
- Please make up with him.
Okay.
Now that we're leaving,
we start thinking about reality.
Right.
That's true. I understand.
Was age a big factor?
No, I just...
casually asked you...
about the future plans,
and it looked like it was too much pressure for you.
That means you were already feeling some type of pressure.
Once I felt that...
(She strongly felt that he was pressured.)
I thought, "What can we do after this?"
"Just be boyfriend and girlfriend?"
If you feel such pressure from the beginning,
I don't see any possibilities that this will work.
I wasn't exactly burdened, though.
I just didn't expect to discuss that with you that day.
I thought we had to...
get familiar first.
We had already expressed our interests,
but we didn't have enough time to talk after that.
That day, I thought it was...
our chance to get closer,
and you said you wanted to talk about serious stuff.
I was like, "Serious stuff? That's pretty sudden."
I didn't feel any pressure. I was just caught off guard.
So, I thought about it, and my mind went blank.
That can also be educated.
He hasn't been educated yet.
Because he's too young.
He's lived 11 years shorter than Ju Hee, so...
- Exactly.
- Right.
- He's not educated yet.
That's so true.
I had taken our relationship seriously,
but once I moved past it and thought about marriage,
my mind went blank.
- Exactly.
- It's natural for him.
But I'm old enough to consider that matter.
You're right.
That's when I started thinking...
- that we wouldn't work.
- Right.
You're right. I understand.
But it's true that you had...
feelings for me...
- when we talked in the Talk Room.
- Yes.
I should be choosing someone I want to keep seeing...
when this ends.
But if you're flustered by that question,
how are we supposed to make progress?
That's the trickiest issue.
Anyway, even after all those conversations,
it wasn't enough to convince me.
So, you don't think our feelings can grow deeper,
and you don't want to picture our future together?
It didn't look like you were picturing our future.
But we could start doing that together.
But we didn't talk about that.
Okay.
I could tell that you were flustered.
That's true. I was flustered.
I didn't expect you to bring that up at that moment.
But I wanted...
our relationship to get more serious.
I never took it lightly.
So, I wanted to picture it together through conversations.
- Why is it so complicated?
- Us?
Why am I...
- Yourself?
- Yes.
All my emotions are tangled up.
He should say something to convince her right now.
I know I'm not good enough.
(I know I'm not good enough.)
But I also have a job, you know?
(Yun So)
I also have a job.
You do.
And if things go well with you,
who knows what will happen to us?
I'm confident that I can make you happy...
and that I can treat you right.
I want you to believe me.
I'm not a shallow person, but you don't take me seriously.
I do take you seriously.
She's feeling better.
- She feels better!
- A little bit.
I do take you seriously.
(Frustrated)
Relationships are tricky.
Anyway, I want you to know...
that I take us seriously...
and that I care about you.
We can always picture...
our future together.
Yes! He knows what to say.
Thanks for understanding.
(Thanks for understanding.)
Whatever your decision is, I won't blame you.
He's good.
But I hope it's good news for me.
That's cute.
Actually, I already like you.
He only says what she wants to hear.
Isn't that the first time...
- he actually said the word "like?" - It is.
This proves that nothing...
- can beat sincerity.
- Right.
Actually, I already like you.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm sorry if I didn't convince you enough.
Oh, man.
She's trying to hold her smile.
(He tells her his honest feelings for the last time.)
Anyway, I said everything I wanted to say.
(Anyway, I said everything I wanted to say.)
I also told you all my honest feelings.
All that's left is your decision.
- I think so.
- Right.
I gave it my entire effort,
and if I fail to convince her,
it just means I'm not good enough for her.
But I'm still into her.
Come on, Yun So.
- I'll be in my room.
- Okay.
You don't have to go.
No, I need some time.
Okay. Get some rest.
Okay.
- This is so sad.
- Why?
No, keep thinking.
Of course, I will. I'll never give up.
Until the last moment!
I was talking to Si Won,
but there was something I decided not to say.
I'll tell you what it was. Si Won is 25 years old, right?
So, even his seniors are...
- like 27 or 28.
- Right.
And imagine them bringing their girlfriends.
They could be 22...
- or 23, 24, 25, 26...
- Oh, right.
I never thought about that.
Right? When I thought about that,
it just occurred to me, "Will this be okay?"
- I never thought about that.
- Right?
And when he meets my friends' boyfriends,
they have social status and standing,
- and they make good money.
- Right.
You're worried he may feel intimidated.
I worry about that too.
That's such a realistic worry.
Yes, those thoughts just hit me.
I was surprised by how serious I could be.
That's the reality.
You really can't ignore...
- the generational gap.
- Exactly.
There are things that people in the same generation...
share together.
Right.
At last, it's the moment of the final decision.
(The final decision is near.)
(Who will the older women...)
(and the younger men choose?)
(The QR Room is open for the final decision.)
When they open the door to the QR Room,
the younger man that chose them will be waiting.
It's entirely up to the woman whether to take his hand...
or walk away.
After seven days,
they only become a real-life couple...
if both show up at the agreed spot.
Who will be matched together?
(How many final couples will there be?)
(It's the day of the final decision. Please head to the QR Room.)
It's the final message.
- I'll be back.
- See you.
(Yu Jin is the first one to head to the QR Room.)
I'm so nervous.
(The walk to the final decision...)
(is more nerve-racking than ever.)
(Who will be waiting for her?)
I hope there's no big surprise.
Why am I so nervous?
(Yu Jin and Si Won both had feelings for each other.)
Smile.
(Cup your face with both hands, and I'll look at you.)
(Are you only looking at me?)
(I wrote you down as my number 1...)
(yesterday.)
(Was I your number 1?)
(Yesterday, you were.)
(Who would you go on a date with tomorrow?)
(Who do you think? Who would you go with?)
(I want to go with the girl...)
(named Choi Yu Jin.)
(Shy)
(I can't wait to see you outside of this.)
(They even promised to meet again after the show.)
They looked so cute together.
(Though they know how each other feels, )
(she feels nervous.)
I can't go inside.
I'm sure he's waiting for her.
(Will Si Won be waiting in the QR Room?)
I can't go inside.
I'm sure he's waiting for her.
(Si Won chose Yu Jin as his final decision.)
(Smiling)
Look at his nice smile.
Coming in here was so nerve-racking.
Hearing your footsteps made my heart flutter like mad.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I thought you wouldn't be in here.
- What? Nonsense.
(The two keep giggling.)
What big, bright smiles from them.
My feelings grew one step at a time.
(My feelings for Yu Jin grew one step at a time.)
My feelings for Yu Jin started growing...
on our way to the pool.
(The two had a shared interest in sports.)
While talking to her,
I had this urge to talk to her more.
We talked...
after the age reveal.
It was nice, so I wanted to go on a date with her.
We had a group date the next day.
As it was loud with all the singing,
we whispered into each other's ears.
Taking photos was when I had the most butterflies in my stomach.
(Si Won's feelings kept growing.)
That expression just now was that of a guy in love.
I chose her without any hesitation.
There was no dilemma.
(Yu Jin slowly stepped into Si Won's heart.)
It was fun at Yeon House thanks to you.
Let's go grab grilled hagfish right away.
(Let's go grab grilled hagfish.)
Okay, I'm in.
- The two look good together.
- Let's go.
Off we go.
(The first final couple, Yu Jin and Si Won)
I'm getting all shy.
- Right? I'm getting shy too.
- Right?
- You're cold, right?
- Yes, extremely.
Let's hurry.
First off, I can't feel...
the age gap when I'm alone with him.
It felt like the two of us were on a similar wavelength.
Everything went smoothly with Si Won...
after spending time at the pool.
Both of us felt that luck was on our side...
and that everything flowed smoothly.
(They took an interest in each other on Day 3.)
Even when we went on a jog.
The weather was great when I went on a jog with Si Won.
Every moment is memorable.
(The day was perfect when I was with Si Won.)
"Are we meant to be?" was what crossed my mind.
(The two became a couple after a series of coincidences.)
Even in Noona Is a Woman to Me Season Two,
we have a couple with a 12-year age gap.
(Yu Jin: 37 years old, Si Won: 25 years old)
In both Season 1 and Season 2,
a couple with a 12-year age gap...
- A 12-year age gap.
- was born.
I can't really feel the 12-year age gap...
- between the two.
- Me neither.
They look like...
- a really happy couple.
- Exactly.
Please be a real couple.
(Ji Hye heads to the final decision QR Room.)
It's Ji Hye, the show's undisputed femme fatale.
As I made my feelings clear to him,
I felt like a burden had been lifted.
(Ji Hye expressed her feelings to Jeong Won.)
Do you mind moving?
(Ji Hye expressed her feelings to Jeong Won from the start.)
(Bolder expressions as time went on)
What are you certain about?
(And a clear-cut confession)
The two look similar and good together.
(After learning about Ji Hye's feelings, )
(did Jeong Won choose her as expected?)
Everything was great for the two.
(Stopping)
(Is no one in the room?)
- No way.
- What?
No, stop lying!
Don't do this to us.
- Don't do this to your family.
- There's more than one guy.
- Two guys?
- I doubt it.
What?
(Jeong Won chose Ji Hye as his final decision.)
What's this?
(Glancing)
(Jeong Won and Jun Han were waiting for Ji Hye.)
- It's Jun Han.
- Jun Han.
See that? Jun Han is very honest about his feelings.
(Jun Han's final choice was Ji Hye.)
I opened the door, thinking Jeong Won...
would be the only one in the room.
But Jun Han was also in there.
I was genuinely surprised.
While talking to Ji Hye...
last night for the last time,
I was completely turned down.
I was already determined to express my feelings...
once I found a person whom I thought...
would be a good match for me.
That turned out to be Jeong Won.
I wanted to leave after hearing...
a clear answer.
I wanted to hear that I wasn't the one.
While being in Yeon House,
Ji Hye was the one who made me laugh the most.
That was why I chose the one...
who made me the happiest as my final decision.
Well done.
(Feeling sorry and grateful)
She's grateful but also embarrassed. I get it.
(And one guy is smiling brightly next to Jun Han.)
I felt confident at that moment.
When it came to Ji Hye,
we spoke the same language, had fun together,
and felt great happiness.
What's more, it felt like her personality...
was that of someone...
who would lead me to the right path when I went astray,
hence why I chose her.
Jeong Won wants someone with a clear older woman charm.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Ji Hye.
I'll make you happy in every moment you share with me...
from now on.
Leave with me.
Is it my turn now?
(Nervous)
The real dopamine comes...
when you make the opposite decision.
I'll make you feel that dopamine rush.
Even his last words are those of Jun Han.
I'm much taller than Jeong Won.
Jun Han is cute. He really is.
- I told you he was cute.
- He's cute.
Jun Han is being humorous until the end.
I now have to make a decision, right?
Thanks to you, I've made many fun memories.
It was fun.
Why do I feel so bad?
Hearing that it was fun is making me cry.
No?
(Tearing up)
(She bid farewell to Jun Han.)
Anyway.
(Next is...)
(Jeong Won.)
Let's get grilled hagfish.
- Grilled hagfish again?
- Are they all craving it?
Is there something to do with it?
Is that like a trending pickup line or what?
It must be like a signal to each other.
(Let's get grilled hagfish.)
(Ji Hye reached her hand out to Jeong Won.)
Bye.
(The second final couple, Ji Hye and Jeong Won)
Aren't you cold?
No, I'm fine.
- Are you?
- Yes.
By the way, I was really surprised.
- Because of Jun Han?
- Yes.
I was too.
I thought you'd be the only one in there.
Only me?
(The two can't help but laugh when together.)
Anyway.
I'm the type who doesn't think too deeply about things.
So my plan is to date him casually outside of Yeon House.
Making a decision after that doesn't seem all that late either.
This final decision doesn't mean, "We must date."
"We're dating starting today."
Dating outside of Yeon House is the real talking stage.
(Will they connect even outside of Yeon House?)
(And another younger man is waiting for an older woman.)
(Jin Wu)
I wasn't certain even as I was waiting for her.
Whether she'll take my hand or not.
I hope things work out for Jin Wu.
(The older woman Jin Wu is anxiously waiting for...)
(is Jin Young.)
As expected.
(Jin Wu chose Jin Young as his final decision.)
Every moment of our date was memorable.
(Jin Wu proactively approached Jin Young after the date.)
How could I not be interested in you...
when you listened to what I said so attentively?
You're the first person I've talked to about such deep topics.
This is my reason.
(This is my reason.)
(Jin Wu tried to give certainty to Jin Young.)
Those moments.
I forgot they had such moments.
I simply wanted to take care of you.
I didn't want you to cry.
(Jin Wu kept knocking on Jin Young's heart until the end.)
(The two face each other.)
(Will Jin Young choose Jin Wu?)
Jin Wu kept making a move on her until the very last moment.
Honestly, Jin Wu was all about Jin Young...
- aside from Ji Hye.
- Exactly.
Since...
we couldn't spend as much time here,
I will make you much happier outside.
(I will make you much happier outside of Yeon House.)
Look. He's going to make...
- Jin Young happy.
- Jin Wu is...
(Jin Young is making a poker face at Jin Wu's confession.)
Please.
What will happen?
(Jin Young thinks about it for longer.)
(Anxious)
I was hoping Jin Young would leave with me.
It's true that we started getting to know each other...
(Nervous)
quite late at Yeon House.
Let's try to get to know...
each other better outside.
(Let's try to get to know each other better outside.)
Come here.
(Grabbing immediately)
(Relieved)
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What is it?
(A touching moment)
- Give her a hug.
- Like so...
(Jin Young and Jin Wu are a couple.)
For real?
I didn't expect this to happen.
(Relieved)
Give her a hug, Jin Wu.
- He's about to cry.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong? What is it?
What's with the sigh?
He can finally relax.
What is it?
Seriously.
(The third final couple, Jin Young and Jin Wu)
Why did you sigh?
Starting the sentence with...
- "It's true that we started..." - Yes?
Almost gave me a heart attack.
Seriously.
I never thought I'd see those two dating.
It's a result I was hoping for,
but little did I expect it...
to come true in the last three days.
This feels like getting into my dream college.
No other words...
can really convey...
what I'm feeling right now.
I was simply curious.
It wasn't because I had a great interest in him or feelings for him.
After choosing him...
"I chose you because of such feelings."
"I'll start getting to know you from now on."
"But that may or may not make my feelings for you grow."
(Jin Young chose out of curiosity, not certain feelings.)
I'm most likely going to let him know that.
If I'm being completely honest, my feelings for him aren't that big.
(7 days later)
That's more than enough.
(Will the two meet?)
(Ju Hee is the last to head to the QR Room.)
It's Ju Hee and Yun So now.
I wonder what Yun So will say to Ju Hee.
(What kind of decision will Ju Hee make?)
That's a smile of confidence.
(The younger man to choose Ju Hee as his final decision is...)
(Yun So.)
The one who stood out the most as soon as I joined Yeon House...
was Ju Hee.
(It was Ju Hee.)
She was pretty...
when I saw her from the side.
(Ever since the first day at Yeon House, he had eyes only on Ju Hee.)
(Once again, )
Come on.
(Yun So chose Ju Hee.)
Hey.
From the start to the end.
(Ju Hee looks determined.)
Yun So only ever had eyes on Ju Hee.
(The two face each other in the final decision.)
You're my first choice even today.
Do you want to grab my hand?
(Will Ju Hee also choose Yun So as her final decision?)
I hope Ju Hee's feelings don't waver.
(Ju Hee doesn't give an immediate answer.)
(Ju Hee and Yun So had an 11-year age gap.)
It felt like if I was more focused...
on the dating part,
you were more focused...
on marriage.
- You're not wrong.
- Right?
It's 50-50.
(Ju Hee had many realistic dilemmas about dating Yun So, )
(a guy 11 years younger.)
(Will Ju Hee take Yun So's hand and leave together?)
What is it? Stop making...
- such a mysterious face.
- What's going on?
Please. I hope nothing else comes into play.
Don't look as if...
- you're about to cry.
- Stop.
You're my first choice even today.
Do you want to grab my hand?
(Do you want to grab my hand?)
Okay.
You were eventually going to take his hand.
(Relieved)
Let's go.
(The fourth final couple, Ju Hee and Yun So)
(Smiling brightly)
They look adorable.
There's a tension between the two,
- making me nervous.
- Exactly.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
I couldn't talk well when you were actually in front of me.
They look good together.
(Their tightly clasped hands)
I kind of hurt Yun So, right?
"What if he's not in the room?"
I opened the door with such concern.
But he was standing there, all cute.
It made me really happy.
(It made me happy.)
I'm the type to think things through for a long time.
We didn't have much time to get to know each other.
I needed...
more time.
(Yun So gave certainty to Ju Hee, who was struggling with dilemmas.)
I hope you'd trust me.
I already like you, Ju Hee.
We talked more after coming to Yeon House.
He assured me in areas that...
I wasn't certain about during those talks.
That was why...
I chose Yun So after much thinking.
During the one week,
Ju Hee was the one who gave me a really hard time.
Even so,
I had feelings for her.
Hence why I confessed to her today.
(Ju Hee who took Yun So's hand)
The two overcame the 11-year age gap hurdle...
and finally became a couple.
These two look so adorable for some reason.
(Four final couples were born on the last night at Yeon House.)
(12-year age gap, Yu Jin and Si Won)
(11-year age gap, Ju Hee and Yun So)
(6-year age gap, Ji Hye and Jeong Won)
(1-year age gap, Jin Young and Jin Wu)
(After deciding on the time and place to meet after 7 days, )
(the final couples leave Yeon House.)
(It's now time to return to their daily life.)
We made great memories together.
I'm leaving with many happy memories.
The moments at Yeon House...
will become a shining memory for me.
(The moments at Yeon House are like shining memories.)
It felt like waking up from a long dream.
The time at Yeon House felt like a dream.
(They left Yeon House with memories each made.)
(Will we be able to meet after 7 days?)
We already spilled the tea that...
there's a real couple...
- among the four couples.
- Right.
How many do you think are real couples?
Four couples left Yeon House just now.
But how many real couples will there be after seven days?
I have a feeling there will be at least three real couples.
DinDin said three couples.
I'm thinking of four couples.
- All four couples?
- Woo Young said four.
Yes, four.
All four could end up being real couples.
(The day of the final decision)
(After leaving Yeon House, )
(where it was full of heart-fluttering moments, )
(the older women and younger men returned to their ordinary lives.)
(After spending a week...)
(in their own realities...)
(Will their feelings for each other remain the same?)
(This is the place Jeong Won and Ji Hye promised to meet.)
Only when they show up at the meeting place...
with mutual feelings for each other,
they become a real couple.
(It's 3pm under the Lone Tree in Olympic Park.)
- It's a beautiful day.
- It's the best time of the year.
(Their meeting time is approaching.)
(Will Jeong Won and Ji Hye be able to meet again...)
It's so nice.
(in this place full of love?)
(It's exactly 3pm, the time they promised to meet.)
(Jeong Won arrives first.)
- It's Jeong Won.
- Jeong Won.
Jeong Won.
(Looking around)
- He brought flowers.
- Jeong Won showed up.
(Will Ji Hye show up too?)
As for me, I don't have much concern...
- about the age difference.
- That's right. Me neither.
But what worries me is this.
Usually, when a younger man and an older woman see each other,
one could have more experience...
while the other doesn't.
- That's true.
- Also, the difference...
- in one's financial sense...
- Okay.
- cannot be ignored.
- Right.
But...
don't worry about me.
(But don't worry about me.)
I just think...
I didn't get to show you...
(I haven't shown you 100 percent of myself.)
all of me.
I believe you'll find many aspects of me charming.
I'm just selling myself once more.
- No need to consider him young.
- Right.
(Word of assurance for Ji Hye who feels anxious)
- You have no regrets, right?
- Right.
If you regret it, tell me now and run.
- No, I have no regrets.
- Okay.
(Will Ji Hye keep the promise?)
What will you do, Ji Hye?
I think she'll show up.
I hope she does.
(Nervous)
(Turning)
(Beaming)
You're here.
(Smiling)
Gosh.
She's here.
- They met after a week.
- Seriously?
They must be so happy to see each other...
since it's been a week.
Hug. Hug each other already!
- How have you been?
Good. How have you been, Ji Hye?
- Good.
- I brought you a gift.
- What is it?
- A perfume.
- Is it for me?
- Yes.
- Really?
I loved its scent.
- Yes. So I bought it.
Nice start, Jeong Won.
(Happy)
- Let's hold hands.
- Let's go somewhere quiet.
- Hold hands? Okay.
- Yes.
Let's show it to the world.
(Holding tightly)
I'll hold this for you.
These flowers are pretty.
- Right? They're pretty.
- Yes, they are.
I didn't know you were a man who could prepare such a thing.
Of course, I am.
Have you given it much thought?
Have you thought it through before you come here?
Yes.
When I look back at my life,
I was a workaholic, addicted to work.
- Right?
- Yes.
Maybe...
while working,
I might get burned out in the future.
Right.
And when I have concerns about my life,
I thought you'd hear them out.
And you'd share it with me.
- Did you think so?
- Yes.
That's the best.
- Do you think I'll be helpful?
- Yes.
I had a strong feeling you'd help me in that situation.
- Really?
- Yes.
Maybe...
my ideal type isn't someone I do business with.
Maybe it's someone who I can have fun living life with.
- Maybe that's my ideal type.
- I see.
- That was what I was thinking.
- My goodness.
What about you?
Actually, I had more concerns than you did.
I'm at a point in my life where I have to think realistically.
That's true.
Right now, we don't think about getting married.
But after seeing you a couple of years,
- I might think differently.
- Right.
If our opinions differ at that point,
it's...
Realistically, we'll have to break up.
That's right.
I'm at an age where I should start thinking about marriage.
What if I regret myself...
after 2 or 3 years for making this choice?
I think...
I know what you worry about.
- What I...
- Right.
What I can say for sure is...
that I'll behave, so you won't worry too much about it.
- I'll make you feel secure.
- Okay.
This is amazing.
Okay. Let's see what will happen in two years.
I'll see if you'll say the same thing.
I just said it openly here.
- Good.
Just like in the Yeon House,
let's keep that chemistry going.
- Okay.
- They look good with each other.
- They're cute.
- Shall we?
Let's go.
- I'm happy for them.
- Crazy.
I'm so happy. Congratulations.
What should we eat?
- Let's eat something tasty.
- Okay.
Go get the grilled hagfish.
I want to take photobooth photos.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Since it's come to this,
why didn't you come in a wedding gown?
Should I borrow it from her?
Exactly. You should have worn a wedding gown.
I was clueless, wasn't I?
We now have a couple...
with a six-year age difference.
(Ju Hee and Yun So agreed to meet...)
- Ju Hee and Yun So.
(at 2pm in a Hangang Park.)
Hangang Park.
(Will they be able to meet while a week has passed?)
What do you think?
I think Yun So will show up for sure.
- But Ju Hee lived...
- I'm concerned.
In the real world for a week.
That's a big deal.
- It must've affected her a lot.
- Yes.
(Sighing)
- What will happen?
- I'm a bit concerned.
I'm a bit worried about Ju Hee.
(Yun So came to the meeting spot as expected.)
Yes. I knew he would come.
Actually,
we had mixed feelings about us until the end.
I don't think there is an absolute guarantee...
that we'll meet after seven days.
(A 24-year-old at the beginning of his career...)
(and a 35-year-old who thinks about marriage)
(They were afraid of and worried about...)
(the realistic problems the faced.)
They had a rollercoaster ride with many ups and downs.
(I don't see a future in you.)
I do have a job.
(The present was more important for Yun So...)
(while the future was for Ju Hee.)
They were so confused even in the Yeon House.
- They were on a rollercoaster ride.
- Yes.
(Yun So is standing alone at the meeting point.)
- Can she come for a meal?
- She's not coming.
Oh, dear.
(It's close to their meeting time, but Ju Hee is nowhere to be found.)
(Looking around)
She's not coming. Oh, no.
I think she's not coming.
(He's more nervous because he knows what Ju Hee worries about.)
But it's so sad to leave each other like this.
- No, they have to be matched.
- I know.
If she wants to end it, she should do it...
- after seeing each other a bit.
- It can't be.
(It's past the meeting time, but Ju Hee isn't here.)
It's over for them.
- Is it over?
- It's over.
No. Come on. Seriously.
(Staring)
What?
Is she here?
(What? Is she here?)
(Staring)
What?
Is she here?
(What? Is she here?)
What?
(Ju Hee shows up at the meeting spot.)
- Gosh.
- What?
(For goodness' sake!)
What is this? Seriously.
(Totally relieved)
She looks so pretty.
Why does she look so pretty?
She has become even prettier in the meantime.
(Falling for her for the 100th time)
(Ju Hee brought flowers just like Yun So.)
- Did you bring flowers?
- Yes.
(They're meeting each other after a week.)
- Mine is smaller.
- I know.
I asked for a small bouquet, but...
Exactly. What is this?
- But...
- It feels like a graduation day.
- What? They're twinning again.
- They wore matching clothes.
I should have bought a bigger one.
(Embarrassed)
No, it's cute.
Have you been well?
How have you been?
I couldn't focus at work.
I mean, time was moving slowly.
Every morning I woke up, I thought of you a lot.
(Touched)
I really missed you.
When I came out, I thought you might not show up.
Me?
Why? I was completely into you.
That wasn't enough?
It was because I acted so indecisively back then.
So you might think you can't handle such a person...
in real life.
- You're right.
- It's okay to have doubts.
That's right.
On the contrary,
I thought about you so much during the past week.
I am more certain about my feelings...
compared to the time when I was in the Yeon House.
Really?
I really do like you.
That was why.
My mind was made up.
- Are you being shy?
- Yes.
What? Is there something over there?
Give her a hug, Yun So.
Exactly.
(Yun So is just happy about this situation.)
Why are you blushing?
Shall we take a walk?
- Let's walk that way.
- Okay.
(They hold hands without hesitation.)
I'm so happy to see you.
Me too.
So? How is it to see me outside the Yeon House?
You look even prettier.
Gosh. I wish they would get married.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
After raising Yun So well.
- This is good.
- What is?
- It's good to see you outside.
- Right?
Of course, it's lovely.
- I like how we met here.
- Yes.
I have a question.
What is it?
Did you tell your parents?
Yes. My parents.
I told them as soon as they got back from overseas.
- But...
- Of course, she's worried.
Gosh. What did they say?
My parents are really cool.
They said,
"As long as you're happy, we're fine with it."
- Really?
- That was what they said.
I was really worried about it.
Yes, that's understandable.
I'm so glad to hear that.
Actually, they responded just the way I expected them to.
"We respect your decision."
They don't care whether the age gap is 11 years or 20 years.
"Twenty years."
(Yun So comforts Ju Hee.)
My parents told me they respect me.
Did you tell your parents?
To some extent.
(Hesitating)
- Of course, you'd be cautious.
- I told them to some extent.
I know you'll feel more pressure.
But I'm confident that I can handle it.
In this aspect, I have a lot to learn from you.
So, I'm excited about our future together.
(I'm excited about our future together.)
What would have happened if you hadn't shown up?
Is it cold? You can wear the jacket.
(35-year-old Ju Hee and 24-year-old Yun So)
Do you want to put it on?
We can't let go of our hands.
What do you want for dinner?
They look so good together.
- A mala dish?
- Let's have a mala dish.
- Okay.
(We have a new couple with an 11-year age gap.)
Gosh. I'm so jealous that it hurts.
(She couldn't hold back her true feelings.)
(That's totally understandable.)
(Another spot to meet in 7 days)
Yu Jin and Si Won.
(Yu Jin and Si Won have promised to meet...)
(at 9pm at Eonju Station.)
- Eonju Station.
- At 9pm at Eonju Station.
(Will they be able to meet again?)
(Their last conversation 7 days ago at the Yeon House.)
What are you going to tell your parents?
- To them? I'll show the photo.
- You'll show them our photo.
- And go, "What do you think?" - Yes.
I don't know how they'll respond after hearing how old I am.
- I don't know either.
- Right.
Gosh. The 12-year age gap.
Should we not tell them?
Of course, they'll be surprised at first, right?
They were very worried.
So...
What are you thinking? Are you willing...
to see me outside the Yeon House?
Yes. I'll be there in a week.
Is that so?
Honestly, I believe...
what happens in a week is the real deal.
- Right. I also think...
- Yes.
- that's the time we start...
- We'll get to know each other.
- to really keep in touch.
- We'll start...
to really get to know each other.
(Will they be able to meet again?)
I like how we're on the same page.
(The meeting time is approaching before we know it.)
(Si Won shows up as promised.)
Si Won, who said he'd come,
comes to the meeting spot first.
- Yes.
- He kept his promise.
We both said that we'd show up...
no matter what.
I think she'll definitely show up.
I know he would've thought much about it,
but he's really here.
And he brought the photo they took together.
(Nervous)
(Will Yu Jin keep her promise to Si Won?)
Now, only Yun Jin needs to show up.
(Meanwhile, at the meeting spot of Jin Wu and Jin Young...)
What?
Is this a different spot?
(It's a photo studio.)
Jin Wu will definitely come.
(Will the two show up at the meeting spot?)
(Jin Wu shows up first.)
Jin Wu is a guy who stands firm.
(Nervous)
(Jin Wu looks especially nervous.)
(Sighing)
(Their last conversation 7 days ago at the Yeon House)
Here is what I'm worried about.
You have strong feelings for me,
but mine aren't as strong.
Our feelings are on very different levels.
So, I...
So,
I don't have a huge crush on you yet,
but I wanted to get to know you a little more.
I was curious about you.
That was why, when it comes to you...
I chose you...
to meet you again and get to know more about you.
But while the level of your feelings is up here,
mine is down here.
What if you get hurt by this difference later on?
They kept me worried.
She might feel sorry at the beginning...
because only one person has expressed his feelings a lot.
(Jin Wu felt anxious until the last moment.)
(In 7 days, has the level of Jin Young's feelings changed?)
Please, Jin Young.
Please.
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin hasn't shown up yet.)
- I think Yu Jin will come.
- Yu Jin.
You never know, though.
(It's 30 minutes past the meeting time.)
Is it 30 minutes past the time?
(But Yu Jin is nowhere to be found.)
No. They have to be matched.
Why isn't she coming?
(The more he waits, the more anxious he gets.)
Don't tell me. No.
(It's way past the meeting time, )
(but Yu Jin doesn't show up.)
- No. They have to become a couple.
- No way.
I want to see the two smile together.
They had such beautiful smiles.
Hold on. Come on. This isn't true.
Is this really happening?
Ju Hee showed up late too.
(Sighing)
- Was she worried a lot?
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- Was Yu Jin worried?
She's not coming.
(He keeps on waiting, but...)
No way.
She really didn't show up.
(In the end, he leaves the spot by himself.)
Really?
(Did she really not show up?)
(Everyone is left in silence by the unbelievable result.)
Come on, Yu Jin.
Seriously?
How could this be?
(Yu Jin couldn't keep her promise after 7 days.)
Goodness. Si Won is going back in the end.
(Why did Yu Jin change her mind?)
I can't think of the reasons...
why you didn't show up.
But I believe you have your reasons, Yu Jin.
I want to be good friends later on.
That's all for me.
Ultimately, I have...
chosen not to make a final decision.
I think the final decision felt like a heavy responsibility to me.
I just want to get to know him in a lighthearted way.
So for me to go to him feeling like this...
and declare that we're a couple...
was something I didn't feel was fair to Si Won.
Since I was older, I felt it was only right that I didn't go to him.
That's why I chose not to make a final decision.
I see.
(Yu Jin and Si Won, the couple with a 12-year age gap, didn't work out.)
For some couples, an age gap means nothing.
But for others,
it can be a huge obstacle.
(For some couples, an age gap can be a huge obstacle.)
(Meanwhile, Jin Young still hasn't shown up.)
Gosh. Please.
I guess she's not coming.
Goodness.
(Jin Wu still waits with hope.)
It's just two couples.
I feel like she'd show up with a big smile. Maybe not.
(Did Jin Young's feelings not change?)
- She's not coming.
- I'm sad.
(Sighing)
(Smiling brightly)
Hey.
She's here! She came!
- What?
- She's here!
Jin Young, what took you so long?
(Smiling)
Jin Young showed up for him.
Right.
(Jin Young rushes over to Jin Wu when she sees him.)
(The two kept their promise from 7 days ago.)
Hey.
Did you wait for me? Let me see.
Are you crying?
Were you waiting for me?
(Tearing up)
Are you crying?
- You're not crying, are you?
- I'm not.
Jin Wu was shocked.
You look even better now.
You look handsome today.
Why did you get here so late?
Did you wait long?
He's close to tears right now.
You lost so much weight.
I've been through a lot emotionally.
You've been through a lot emotionally?
I should feed you more...
so you can put on some weight.
- Let's go inside.
- Let's go and take pictures.
What's going on with you?
(Jin Young comforts Jin Wu.)
Goodness.
Why are you shaking so much?
- Why are you about to cry?
- I'm not crying.
Why did you get here so late?
Did you think I wasn't coming?
I didn't think you were coming.
Can you hold my hand?
- You look pretty today.
- What?
I look pretty today?
- Am I pretty?
- You're pretty.
- My nose is running.
- We're taking pictures today.
- Jin Wu.
- Yes?
- I'm good. I feel good.
- You feel good?
I feel like I'm dreaming right now.
You really thought about things a lot over the past week.
Yes, you were all I could think about.
Really? For me,
I actually had to go back to work the very next day.
So...
I barely had time to think about...
what happened at Yeon House.
But more and more,
I found myself wanting to talk to you.
Wanting to hang out with you.
Goodness.
Thinking about things that we'd have fun doing together.
I kept having these thoughts.
I actually already planned out...
what we should do today...
after we take the pictures.
We can do them all. I won't go home tonight.
I mean, you should still go home.
I'll head home after sunrise.
I'll take the first subway home.
Anyway, I kept wanting to spend time with you.
The more I thought about it, the more I realized...
how comfortable I felt with you.
- Right.
- And...
I was really grateful for how you always took care of me.
I think what I loved most was...
how consistently you...
looked out for me.
At the end, you said...
Gosh, I can't believe they worked out.
That it felt like I was moving at a completely different speed.
But I want you to believe this one thing.
I'm not someone who suddenly gets passionate...
and then cools off.
I'm just someone who always has a warm heart.
That's how I want to be, and that's who I'll continue to be.
So I just...
hope you'll have more faith in me.
I guess I'll see as we spend more time together.
Yes.
I'm so happy for them.
If I had to pick the most exciting moment...
I had at Yeon House,
honestly, it was when we took pictures together.
I was pretty forward, wasn't I?
When you came right up to me asking to take pictures,
I felt butterflies in my stomach.
Should we recreate the picture...
we took last time?
Okay.
- Jin Young, you should...
- Are you sure about this?
- Are you really sure about this?
- Plant a kiss on her cheek.
- Is this okay?
- Gosh, this looks good.
Really kiss her cheek now.
Gosh, you're good at this.
They took the picture. He kissed her cheek.
(Compared to 7 days ago, )
(the atmosphere between them is noticeably different.)
They look so good.
Gosh, that's a pretty picture.
- It's so picturesque.
- It feels different than last time.
They really seem like a couple now.
(An older woman-younger man couple with a 1-year age gap is formed.)
(Revealing the real couples who are still together to this day)
What?
- Wait.
- Right now?
(Everyone's eager to find out who they are.)
It feels like I'm taking home a puppy I've just adopted.
I came here hoping to find someone I love,
and I'm leaving here having found that person.
I've realized that age really is just a number.
Yes, I knew...
those two were going to be such a sweet couple.
- They look so good together.
- Right.
Look at them dressed up in school uniforms.
Yun So and I have an 11-year age gap.
- Goodness.
- I'm so happy for them.
We'll just have to do our best.
Ju Hee looks younger.
See? That's what love does.
I really like you, Ju Hee.
After meeting you,
I stopped caring about age.
You might be the person who made me realize age really isn't important.
- Gosh, - These look like wedding photos.
I still like her so much.
We'll keep enjoying our time together and see where it goes.
I got to make great memories...
and I found my partner.
She said "partner."
It was such a meaningful experience.
- Looks like they went on a trip.
- They even traveled together.
(A total of 3 couples were formed, )
(with age gaps of 1, 6, and 11 years.)
I'm so happy for them.
(A total of 3 couples were formed.)
(Congratulations, everyone.)
- Gosh.
- That's amazing.
Our show is the best.
There are three real couples.
With age gaps of 1, 6, and 11 years.
I love it. This is great.
Age feels like such a huge issue sometimes,
- but then I wonder if...
- Right.
It really matters when it comes to love.
Looking at these final couples,
I realized there really isn't one right answer...
if you love someone.
So, has your romantic side come back to life, Woo Young?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
It really has.
- I'm actually so jealous.
- Right?
I'm jealous.
But I also wish we could have seen Yu Jin and Si Won...
and see how things are going for the couples in the real world.
- That's why we've prepared...
- Yes?
A special commentary episode to hear what happened...
between the older women and younger men after the show.
This isn't the end of the show. There's more.
You can watch the Season 2 commentary episode...
on KBS2 and Wavve.
Please look forward to the commentary episode.
And everyone,
- go find love.
- Go find love.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
We'll be cheering you on!
Congratulations!
(It's been 3 months since they left Yeon House.)
Do we sit here?
I'm nervous. It's been a while.
(He's adorable.)
On the cheek?
(Now together as real couples, )
(the older women and younger men have gathered once again.)
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won, the chemistry-packed couple, )
(start off with a sigh.)
Watching the show, I saw him behind the scenes...
That was AI.
How can I let him loose outside?
(From real-life bickering)
How do you feel when you see me and Jeong Won on a date?
I don't like it.
Don't watch.
No, don't watch.
My blood pressure. Somebody get me some medicine.
(My blood pressure. Somebody get me some medicine.)
Yun So, do you still think Ju Hee is like a fairy?
She just keeps getting more and more beautiful.
(She just keeps getting more and more beautiful.)
I think it was love at first sight for me.
(Yun So and Ju Hee are still as sweet as ever.)
If a younger man says he'd give me his liver...
- I'll give you my liver.
- What?
- Gosh, Si Won.
- Goodness.
Should we go back to Yeon House?
I would have chosen you if you had said this back then.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The behind-the-scenes stories of the couples...)
(that couldn't be shown on Noona is A Woman to Me Season 2)
(Now available on Wavve)